Guide to the Elizabeth Jenks Clark Collection of Margaret Anderson
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Personal Papers, 1941-1973; Series VI; 0.42; (1 box)
  - Margaret Anderson's address book, circa 1960-1973 (Box 25, Folder 413)
  - Solita Solano's diary and address book, 1941-1973, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 414-415)
  - Clippings, 1897, 1965, 1969, circa 1972 (Box 25, Folder 416)
  - Miscellaneous subscription notices, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 417)
  - Map of Margaret Anderson's property in Orgeval, France, 1963
  - Various piano and voice scores, manuscript and printed, undated
- Mathilda Hills Papers, 1971-1998; Series VII; 0.42; (1 box)
  The series contains material created and collected by Mathilda Hills that relates to her research on Margaret Anderson in preparation for a biography. Miscellaneous materials filed at the end of the series are arranged in the order in which they were received by the library.
  - Correspondence with Maxine Benoit Jeannn, 1997-1998 (Box 26, Folder 418)
    Removed from Georgette Leblanc by Maxine Benoit Jeannn
  - Letter from Anderson to Hills, 1971 September 16 (Box 26, Folder 418a)
  - Research files
    - Dean, Harriet, 1974, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 419)
    - Gurdjieff, Georges Ivanovitch, undated (Box 26, Folder 420)
    - Heap, Jane, undated (Box 26, Folder 421)
    - Leblanc, Georgette, undated (Box 26, Folder 422)
      Includes performance program and advertisement
  - Clippings, 1979, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 423)
  - Miscellaneous, 1971-1990, undated (Box 26, Folder 424)
    Includes photocopies of Margaret Anderson Trust deed of trust; photocopies of correspondence from other research institutions; dust jacket; and map of Margaret Anderson's property in Orgeval, France.
  - Empty labeled folders (Box 26)
- Oversize
  - "Daring Questions for Thinking People" from American Fabrics (Series II), undated (Box 27 (Oversize), Folder 425)
  - My Thirty Year's War, reviews (Series II), 1930 (Box 27 (Oversize), Folder 426)
  - "Light occupations of the editor, while there is nothing to edit," cartoon from Little Review (Series II), undated (Box 27 (Oversize), Folder 427)
  - Map of Margaret Anderson's property in Orgeval, France (Series VI), 1963 (Box 27 (Oversize), Folder 428)
  - Clippings (Series VI), 1965, undated (Box 27 (Oversize), Folder 429-430)
  - Miscellaneous (Series VII), 1971-1990, undated (Box 27 (Oversize), Folder 431)
  - Various piano and voice music (Series VI), undated (Box 28 (Oversize), Folder 432)
  - Album (Series IV), undated (Box 28 (Oversize), Folder 433)
  - "Chambre d'Hotel," galley (Series II), circa 1972 (Box 29 (Oversize), Folder 434)
  - Clippings (Series VII), 1976-1984 (Box 29 (Oversize), Folder 435)
- Restricted Fragile
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted fragile material. For further information consult Access Services.
  - Box 6, folder 86 (Box 30, Folder 436)
  - Box 8, folder 156 (Box 30, Folder 437)
  - Box 9, folder 170 (Box 30, Folder 438)
  - Box 10, folder 197 (Box 30, Folder 439)
  - Boxes 23 and 24 (Box 31)
  - Box 25, folder 416 (Box 32 (Oversize), Folder 440)